Finding Aid for President (University of Michigan) records, 1967-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical Files 1967/68-2008/09
  - 1999-2000
    - Development, Vice President for
      - General (Box 349)
      - Corporations (Box 349)
      - Events (Box 349)
      - Foundations (Box 349)
      - President's Advisory Group (Box 349)
    - Diversity (Box 349)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief
      - General (Box 349)
      - Investments and Insurance (Box 349)
      - Parking Operations (Box 349)
      - Plant (Box 349)
      - Public Safety (Box 349)
      - Tobacco (Box 349)
    - Flint Campus
      - General (Box 349)
      - Personnel Information (Box 328)
    - General Counsel
      - General (Box 349)
      - Restricted (Box 328)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for
      - General (Box 349)
      - Community Relations (Box 349)
      - Federal Relations (Box 349)
      - State Relations (Box 349)
    - Grievances (Box 328)
    - Higher Education (Box 349)
    - Human Resources
      - General (Box 349)
      - Payroll (Box 349)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 349)
    - Honorary Degrees
      - General (Box 349)
      - Aharon Barak (Box 349)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 350)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 350)
    - Institutes (Box 350)
    - International Issues (Box 350)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 350)
      - Exchange Programs (Box 350)
      - Midwest Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA) (Box 350)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 350)
    - Invitations (Box 350)
    - Libraries
      - Bentley (Box 350)
      - Clements (Box 350)
      - Ford (Box 350)
      - University Library (Box 350)
    - Media (Box 350)
    - Medical Affairs (Box 350)
    - Medical Center (including Vice Provost for)
      - General (Box 350)
      - Hospitals (Box 350)
      - Hospital Executive Board (Box 350)
    - Michigan, State of
      - General (Box 350)
    - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (Box 350)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 350)
    - Michigan Virtual University (Box 350)
    - Millennium Program
      - Imagining America (White House Millennium Council), 2 folders (Box 350)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 351)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 351)
    - Museum
      - Art (Box 351)
    - Musical Society, University (UMS)
      - General (Box 351)
      - Royal Shakespeare Company (Box 351)
    - National Association of State University and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 351)
    - President's Office (Box 351)
    - Presidents Council of State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM) (Box 351)
    - Professorships and endowed Chairs (Box 351)
    - Rankings (Box 351)
    - Regents
      - General (Box 351)
      - David Brandon (Box 351)
      - Lawrence Deitch (Box 351)
      - Rebecca McGowan (Box 351)
      - Philip Power (Regent Emeritus) (Box 351)
      - S. Martin Taylor (Box 351)
      - Katherine White (Box 351)
    - Research, Vice President for (Box 351)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 351)
      - DRDA (Box 351)
    - ROTC (Box 351)
    - SACUA (Box 351)
    - Scholarships
      - General (Box 351)
      - Bentley, 2 folders (Box 351)
    - Search (Box 352)
    - Science Coalition (Box 352)
    - Secretary of the University (Box 352)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 352)
      - Michigamua, 2 folders (Box 352)
      - Naked Mile (Box 352)
    - Students
      - General (Box 352)
      - Student Life Survey (Prepared by UM Substance Abuse Research Center) (Box 352)
      - Student Mothers (Box 352)
      - Student Publications (Box 352)
    - Surveys (Box 352)
    - Tanner Lectures (Box 352)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred (Box 352)
    - Tuition and Fees (Box 352)
    - Undergraduate Education (Box 352)
    - United States
      - Education, Department of (Box 352)
    - Universitas 21 (Box 352)
    - Washtenaw United Way (Box 352)
    - Women
      - General (Box 352)
  - 2000-2001
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President and Provost for (Box 355)
      - General
        - General, 3 folders (Box 355)
          [ER RESTRICTED until July 1, 2030 ]
        - Student Information (Box 469)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2076 ]
      - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 469)
      - Financial Aid, 2 folders (Box 469)
      - Internet Learning (Box 355)
      - Registrar's Office, 2 folders; 2 zip disks included (Box 469)
      - Residency (Box 469)
    - Academic Program Group (APG) (Box 355)
    - Accreditation, 2 folders (Box 355)
    - Affirmative Action: Lawsuit (Box 355)
    - Alumni Association (Box 355)
    - American -- General (Box 355)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 355)
    - Ann Arbor (Box 355)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU), 4 folders (Box 355)
    - Association of Governing Boards (AGB) (Box 355)
    - Associations -- Miscellaneous (Box 355)
    - Athletics (Box 356)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 356)
      - Big Ten, 2 folders (Box 356)
      - Code of Conduct, 3 folders (Box 356)
      - Equity in Athletics Disclosure Act (Box 356)
      - NCAA, 2 folders (Box 357)
      - Sweatshop Advisory Committee (Box 357)
    - Awards
      - General, 2 folders (Box 357)
      - External (Box 357)
      - Hopwood (Box 357)
      - Henry Russel (Box 357)
      - Wallenberg (Box 357)
    - Bollinger, Lee C.
      - General, 2 folders (Box 357)
      - Notes (Box 357)
      - Personal, 4 folders (Box 357)
    - Budget (Box 358)
      - University, 2 folders (Box 358)
    - Business Higher Education Forum (Box 358)
    - Campus
      - General (Box 358)
      - Arthur Miller Theatre (Box 358)
      - Royal Shakespeare Company (RSC) (Box 358)
    - Campus Compact (Box 358)
    - Centers
      - General (Box 358)
      - Ginsberg Center for Community Service and Learning (Box 358)
    - Commencement (Box 358)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 358)
    - Communications, Vice President for, 2 folders (Box 358)
    - Community Service, 2 folders (Box 358)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 358)
    - Conferences and Meetings (Box 358)
    - Congratulations and Commendations (Box 358)
    - Dearborn Campus (Box 469)
      [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2031 ]
    - Detroit (Box 359)
    - Development, Vice President for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - Campaign (Box 359)
      - Corporations (Box 359)
      - Events (Box 359)
      - Foundations, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - President's Advisory Group (Box 359)
      - Prospects (Box 359)
    - Disabled Persons (Box 359)
    - Diversity (Box 359)
    - Economic Development Council (Box 359)
    - Fellowships (Box 359)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief
      - General, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - Financial Operations (Box 359)
      - Investments and Insurance, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - Parking Operations, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - Plant, 2 folders (Box 359)
      - Plant Extension (Box 359)
      - Public Safety (Box 359)
    - Flint Campus (Box 360)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 360)
      - Personnel Information (Box 469)
    - Ford, Gerald (Box 360)
    - Free Speech (background material included) (Box 360)
    - General Counsel, 3 folders (Box 469)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2101 ]
    - Government Relations, Vice President for
      - General (Box 360)
      - Community Relations (Box 360)
      - Federal Relations (Box 360)
      - State Relations (Box 360)
    - Higher Education (Box 360)
    - Honorary Degrees (includes information on recipient Vaclav Havel, President of the Czech Republic) (Box 360)
    - Human Resources
      - General (Box 469)
      - Faculty (Box 469)
        [PR RESTRICTED July 1, 2031 ]
      - Searches (Box 360)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 360)
    - Humanities
      - General, 2 folders (Box 360)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS) (Box 361)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 361)
      - Covisint (Box 361)
      - Fathom (Box 361)
    - Institutes (Box 361)
    - International Issues
      - General (Box 361)
      - Exchange Programs, 2 folders (Box 361)
    - Introduction, Letters of (Box 361)
    - Invitations (Box 361)
    - Journalism -- Michigan Journalism Fellows (Box 361)
    - K-12 (Box 361)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 361)
    - Libraries
      - General (Box 361)
      - Bentley (Box 361)
      - Clements (Box 361)
      - Ford (Box 361)
      - University Library (Box 361)
    - Life Sciences (4 folders; includes materials from academic year 1999/2000) (Box 361)
    - Media (includes report from the Commercial Notetaking Committee) (Box 362)
    - Medical Affairs (Box 362)
    - Medical Center (including Vice Provost for)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 362)
      - Hospital Executive Board, 4 folders (Box 362)
      - Hospitals (Box 362)
    - Medical Institute: Howard Hughes (Box 362)
    - Memberships (Box 362)
    - Michigan, State of
      - General, 2 folders (Box 362)
      - Education, Department of (Box 362)
      - Management and Budget, Department of (Box 362)
      - Senators and Representatives (Box 362)
    - Michigan Economic Development Corporation (MEDC0
      - General (Box 362)
      - Government Relations: State (Box 362)
    - Michigan Schools and Colleges (Box 362)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 362)
    - Michigan Virtual University (Box 362)
    - Michigan Universities Consortium for International Activities (MUCIA) (Box 362)
    - Millennium Program (Box 362)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice Provost for
      - General (Box 362)
      - Martin Luther King, Jr. (MLK) Day (Box 362)
      - President's Advisory Commission (PACMA) (Box 362)
    - Museum
      - General (Box 362)
      - Art (2 folders; includes planning materials and reports on the expansion of the UMMA) (Box 362)
    - Musical Society, University (UMS), 2 folders (Box 363)
    - National Association of State University and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 363)
    - Presidential Initiatives Fund (Box 363)
    - Presidents Council of State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM) (Box 363)
    - Presidents Emeritus (Box 363)
    - President's Information Revolution (includes draft of "The President's Information Revolution Commission Summary Report) (Box 363)
    - Professorships and Endowed Chairs (Box 363)
    - Regents
      - General (includes a report and recommendations from the University's Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on Tobacco Investments) (Box 363)
      - Deane Baker (Box 363)
      - David Brandon (Box 363)
      - Lawrence Deitch (Box 363)
      - Daniel Horning (Box 363)
      - Olivia Maynard (Box 363)
      - Rebecca McGowan (Box 363)
      - Andrea Fischer Newman (Box 363)
      - Philip Power (Box 363)
      - Regent Emeritus -- Frederick Matthaei (Box 363)
      - James Waters (Box 363)
    - Research, Vice President for
      - General, 3 folders (Box 363)
        (includes material on decommissioning the Ford Nuclear Reactor, and the annual report for the Michigan Memorial Phoenix Project)
      - Division of Research Development and Administration (DRDA), 2 folders (Box 363)
      - Venture Capital (Box 363)
    - ROTC (Reserve Officers Training Corps) (Box 364)
    - Scholarships
      - General (Box 364)
      - Bentley (Box 364)
      - Search (Box 364)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 364)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 364)
      - Greeks (Box 364)
      - Housing (Box 364)
      - Michigamua (Box 364)
      - Student Space Policies (Box 364)
      - University Health (Box 364)
    - Students
      - General (Box 364)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) (Box 364)
    - Surveys (Box 364)
    - Tanner Lectures (Box 364)
    - Taubman, A. Alfred (Box 364)
    - Thank You (Box 364)
    - Tuition and Fees (Box 364)
    - Undergraduate Education (Box 364)
    - United States
      - General, 2 folders (Box 364)
      - Education, Department of (Box 364)
    - Universitas 21, 2 folders (Box 364)
    - University Press (Box 365)
    - Washtenaw
      - General (Box 365)
      - United Way (Box 365)
    - Women, 2 folders (Box 365)
  - 2001-2002
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President and Provost for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 366)
      - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 469)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2077 ]
      - Financial Aid, 2 folders (Box 469)
      - Registrar, 2 folders (Box 366)
      - Residency, 2 folders (Box 469)
    - Academic Program Group (Box 366)
    - Accreditation (Box 366)
    - Alumni Association (Box 366)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 366)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 367)
      - Folders 1-4 of 5 (Box 367)
      - Folder 5 of 5 (Box 367)
    - Athletics
      - General, 3 folders (Box 367)
      - Big Ten, 3 folders (Box 367)
      - Board in Control of Intercollegiate Athletics (BICIA) (Box 367)
      - Code of Conduct (Box 367)
      - NCAA, 3 folders (Box 368)
    - Awards
      - General (Box 368)
      - External (Box 368)
      - Henry Russel (Box 368)
      - Hopwood (Box 368)
    - Bollinger, Lee C.
      - General (Box 368)
      - Notes (Box 368)
      - Personal, 5 folders (Box 368)
      - Quotes (Box 368)
    - Budget, 2 folders (Box 368)
    - Campus -- Arthur Miller Theatre (Box 369)
    - Campus Compact (Box 369)
    - Centers (Box 369)
    - Commencement (Box 369)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation (CIC) (Box 369)
    - Communications, Vice President for, 2 folders (Box 369)
    - Community Service (Box 369)
    - Condolences and Get-Well Wishes (Box 369)
    - Congratulations and Commendations (Box 369)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - General (Box 369)
      - Henry Ford Estate (Box 369)
    - Development, Vice President for
      - General (Box 369)
      - Campaign (Box 369)
      - Corporations (Box 369)
      - Events (Box 369)
      - Foundations (Box 369)
      - President's Advisory Group (Box 369)
    - Disabled Persons (Box 369)
    - Diversity (Box 369)
    - Environment -- President's Advisory Committee on Environment (PACE) (Box 369)
    - Fellowships (Box 369)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief (Box 370)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 370)
      - Financial Operations (Box 370)
      - Parking Operations (Box 370)
      - Plant, 2 folders (Box 370)
      - Public Safety (Box 370)
    - Flint Campus
      - General, 2 folders (Box 370)
      - Student Information (Box 469)
    - Ford, Gerald (Box 370)
    - Free Speech (Box 370)
    - General Counsel, 3 folders (Box 470)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2102 ]
    - Government Relations, Vice President for
      - General (Box 370)
      - Community Relations (Box 370)
      - Federal Relations, 2 folders (Box 370)
      - State Relations, 3 folders (Box 370)
    - Graduate Student Assistants (Box 370)
    - Higher Education, 2 folders (Box 370)
    - Honorary Degrees (Box 370)
    - Human Resources (Box 371)
      - General, 3 folders (Box 470)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2032 ]
      - Faculty, 4 folders (Box 470)
      - Staff Benefits, 2 folders (Box 470)
    - Humanities, 3 folders (Box 371)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 371)
    - Institutes (Box 371)
    - International Issues, 3 folders (Box 371)
    - Journalism -- Michigan Journalism Fellows (Box 371)
    - W. K. Kellogg Foundation (Box 371)
    - Libraries
      - General (Box 371)
      - Bentley (Box 371)
      - Clements (Box 371)
      - Ford (Box 371)
      - University Library (Box 371)
    - Life Sciences, 3 folders (Box 371)
    - Medical Center (including Vice-Provost for) (Box 372)
      - General (Box 372)
      - Hospital Executive Board, 3 folders (Box 372)
      - Hospitals (Box 372)
    - Memberships (Box 372)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 372)
    - Minority Affairs, Vice Provost for (Box 372)
    - Museum
      - Art (UMMA) (Box 372)
      - Exhibit (Box 372)
    - Musical Society, University (UMS) (Box 372)
    - National Association of State University and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC), 2 folders (Box 372)
    - National Science Foundation (NSF) (Box 372)
    - Presidents Council of State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM) (Box 373)
    - President's Office (Box 373)
    - Regents
      - General (Box 373)
      - Registrar's Office (Box 373)
    - Research, Vice President for
      - General, 3 folders (Box 373)
      - DRDA, 2 folders (Box 373)
    - Scholarships
      - General, 2 folders (Box 373)
      - Bentley (Box 373)
    - Search (Box 373)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 373)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for (Box 374)
      - General (Box 374)
      - Greeks (Box 374)
      - Housing, 2 folders (Box 374)
      - Michigan Union (Box 374)
      - Space Policy (Box 374)
    - Student Publications (Box 374)
    - Students
      - General (Box 374)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (Box 374)
    - Surveys (Box 374)
    - Tanner Lectures (Box 374)
    - United States
      - General (Box 374)
      - Education, Department of (Box 374)
    - Universitas 21 (Box 374)
    - University of Michigan -- General (Box 374)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 374)
    - Washtenaw United Way (Box 374)
    - White, B. Joseph
      - General (Box 374)
      - Memberships (Box 374)
      - Personal (Box 374)
      - Speeches (Box 374)
    - Women (2 folders; includes an endorsement for the National Council for Research on Women publication Balancing the Equation, written by Lee Bollinger) (Box 374)
  - 2002-2003
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President and Provost for
      - General (Box 376)
      - Admissions (Box 470)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2078 ]
      - Financial Aid (Box 470)
      - Registrar (Box 470)
      - Residency (Box 376)
    - Academic Program Group (Box 376)
    - Accreditation
      - General (Box 376)
      - College Boards (Box 376)
    - Alumni Association (Box 376)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 376)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 376)
    - Athletics
      - General, 2 folders (Box 376)
      - Big Ten, 2 folders (Box 377)
      - Board in Control (Box 377)
      - Code of Conduct (Box 377)
      - Equity in Athletics Disclosure Act (Box 377)
      - NCAA, 2 folders (Box 377)
    - Awards
      - General (Box 377)
      - Henry Russel (Box 377)
      - Hopwood (includes Donald Hall poem) (Box 377)
    - Budget
      - Budget Plan (Box 377)
      - University (Box 377)
    - Calendar (Box 377)
    - Campus -- General (Box 377)
    - Campus Compact (Box 377)
    - Centers (Box 378)
      - General (Box 378)
      - Center for the Education of Women (CEW) (Box 378)
    - Coleman, Mary Sue
      - General (Box 378)
      - Boards (Box 378)
      - Notes (Box 378)
      - Personal (Box 378)
      - Speeches, 2 folders (Box 378)
    - Communications, Vice President for, 2 folders (Box 378)
    - Community (Box 378)
    - Congratulations and Commendations (Box 378)
    - Dearborn Campus
      - General (Box 378)
      - Fairlane Training and Development Center (FTDC) (Box 378)
    - Development, Vice President for (Box 379)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 379)
      - Campaign (Box 379)
      - Corporations (Box 379)
      - Events (Box 379)
      - Foundations (Box 379)
      - Kellogg Foundation (Box 379)
      - Legal Services (Box 379)
      - President's Advisory Group (Box 379)
      - Prospects (Box 379)
    - Diversity (Box 379)
    - Environment (Box 379)
    - Facilities (Box 379)
    - Fellowships (Box 379)
    - Financial Officer, Vice President and Chief
      - General, 2 folders (Box 379)
      - Divestment, 3 folders (Box 379)
      - Financial Operations (Box 379)
      - Investments and Insurance, 2 folders (Box 379)
      - Parking and Transportation (Box 380)
      - Plant and Operations (Box 380)
      - Public Safety (Box 380)
      - Purchasing/Stores (Box 380)
    - Flint Campus (Box 380)
    - Ford, Gerald (Box 380)
    - General Counsel, 3 folders (Box 471)
      [CR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2103 ]
    - Gifts (Box 380)
    - Government Relations, Vice President for
      - Community (Box 380)
      - Federal (Box 380)
      - State (Box 380)
    - Graduate Student Instructors (Box 380)
    - Higher Education (Box 380)
    - History and Traditions (Box 380)
    - Honorary Degree (Box 380)
    - Human Resources
      - General (Box 380)
      - Faculty and Staff, 2 folders (Box 471)
        [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2033 ]
      - Payroll (Box 380)
      - Staff Benefits (Box 380)
    - Humanities
      - General (Box 380)
      - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (AAAS) (Box 380)
    - Information Technology, Vice Provost for (Box 380)
    - Infrastructure (Report of the National Science Foundation Blue-Ribbon Advisory Panel on Cyberinfrastructure) (Box 380)
    - Institutes (Box 380)
    - International, 4 folders (Box 381)
      (includes external review committee report on the Center for Japanese Studies)
    - Journalism -- Michigan Journalism Fellows (Box 381)
    - Libraries
      - Bentley (Box 381)
      - Clements (Box 381)
      - University (Box 381)
    - Life Sciences (Box 381)
    - Medical Center (including Vice-Provost for)
      - General, 3 folders (Box 381)
      - Hospital Executive Board, 3 folders (Box 381)
      - Howard Hughes Medical Institute (Box 381)
      - Patient Information (Box 471)
    - Memberships (Box 382)
    - Michigan Society of Fellows (Box 382)
    - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA) (Box 382)
    - Millennium Program -- Imagining America (Box 382)
    - Minority Affairs (Box 382)
    - Museums
      - General (Box 382)
      - Art (UMMA) (Box 382)
    - Musical Society, University (UMS) (Box 382)
    - National Association of State University and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) (Box 382)
    - Presidents Council of State Universities of Michigan (PCSUM) (Box 382)
    - President's Office
      - Funding Requests (Box 382)
      - Invitations, 2 folders (Box 382)
    - Professorships and Endowed Chairs (Box 383)
    - Regents, 2 folders (Box 383)
    - Research, Vice President for
      - General, 3 folders (Box 383)
      - DRDA (Box 383)
      - Openness and Security Policies (Box 384)
    - Scholarships
      - General (Box 384)
      - Bentley (Box 384)
    - Searches (Box 384)
    - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) (Box 384)
    - Student Affairs, Vice President for
      - General (Box 384)
      - Health Service (Box 384)
      - Housing (Box 384)
    - Students (Box 384)
    - Surveys (Box 384)
    - Tuition (Box 384)
    - Unions -- Michigan League (Box 384)
    - United States
      - General (Box 384)
      - Education, Department of (Box 384)
      - Energy, Department of (Box 384)
    - United Way
      - Chicago (Box 384)
      - Washtenaw (Box 384)
    - University of Michigan Press (Box 384)
    - Women
      - General, 2 folders (Box 384)
      - Gender in Science and Engineering Committee (Box 384)
      - President's Advisory Commission on Women's Issues (PACWI) (Box 384)
  - 2003-2004
    - Academic Affairs, Vice President and Provost for
      - General, 2 folders (Box 386)
      - Admissions, 2 folders (Box 471)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2079 ]
      - Financial Aid (Box 471)
      - Registrar (Box 386)
      - Residency (Box 386)
    - Academic Program Group (APG) (Box 386)
    - Accreditation (Box 386)
    - Advancement of University Initiatives -- On Diversity and Gender Equity (Box 386)
    - Alumni Association (Box 386)
    - American Academy of the Arts and Sciences (AAAS) (Box 386)
    - American Council on Education (ACE) (Box 386)
    - American Council of Learned Societies (ACLS) (Box 386)
    - Arts and Humanities (Box 386)
    - Association of American Universities (AAU) (Box 386)